onnanoko hajimemashita
A tired girl starts her day
tameiki wa bioron no shirabe ni nite
With a sigh like the moan of a violin
akai mi hajikechatta
A cherry bursts in her mouth
mada anata wo shiranai
This was before we had met
konna koto hajimetette
This is the first time I've ever felt like this
manazashi wa aku no hana sakimidarete mo
I could see that your pretty eyes were filled with contempt
ie e to tsuzuku
But I had to go home
basu sutoppu demo anata wa tsurenai
Even at the bus stop, you gave me the cold shoulder
karameta hanabi myaku utsu
The fireworks in the sky pulse
koi no shiruetto
In a silhouette of love
karui mahou
With a little magic,
usotsuki na kuchibiru
Two sets of lying lips
sou kasaneteru
Lock together
ano ne
You see
nee kamisama
God...
warui ko ni naritai yo
I'd like to be a naughty girl
ii ko ni shiteru kara
I'm tired of being good
onegai dayo
So, please
zurui koto sasetoite
It's for a good reason
ii koto shitai nara
So let me be bad for once
sukaato hirogaesu shite
By flipping my skirt
sugu kaeru yo
I'll be back soon
doyoubi wa haresou da
It looks like Saturday is going to be sunny
kamisama hajimemashita
God, it has already started
With the bright, clear sky above her and a light heart, she is off for a little shopping in town.
（講釈師）
空も晴れ晴れ 心も軽く
ちょっと街まで お買い物
（奈々生(ななみ)）
ええと 歯磨き粉にスポンジ
それから ガムテープ
Let's see. I need toothpaste, a sponge, and also some packing tape.
（男の子１）
おい 誰か下りてきたぞ
Hey, someone's coming.
（男の子１）
で… 出た！
G-Ghost!
（男の子２）
逃げろ！
Run!
What the heck was that?
（奈々生）
何よ あれ
Seriously, what was up with that? That wasn't very nice.
（講釈師）
ホント何だってのよ　感じ悪…
Nanami Quits Being A God
Supermarket
Have you heard about that old,
rundown shrine on top of the mountain?
（女性１）
山の上に
野ざらしの廃神社があるじゃない
The one they say is haunted?
Household Goods
（女性２）
人だまが出るって言われてた
あそこ？
（女性１）
そうそう あの お化け神社
Yes, that's the one.
People say they've seen the ghost of a young girl up there lately.
Household Goods
最近じゃ
若い女の子の幽霊が出るとか
（女性２）
やだ 怖い
Wow, that's spooky.
I know!
（女性１）
ホントよね
子供にも行くなって言ってるのよ
I've told my kids not to go there too.
何かあったら大変だし
I mean, it would be terrible if something happened.
It...
（奈々生）
そ…
そんな気味悪い所じゃないです！
It's not creepy up there at all!
立地は少し不便だけど
毎日 巴衛(ともえ)が きれいにしてるし―
It's a bit out of the way, but Tomoe keeps it clean every day, and it's not rundown at all.
廃神社なんかじゃないです！
O-Oh, it's not?
あ… あら そうなの
Tomoe?
巴衛？
Register
（女性２）ごめんなさいね
（女性たち）オホホ…
I'm so sorry.
Hahaha
Ah!
（奈々生）
お化け神社
Abandoned and haunted?
I don't think it looks rundown at all.
廃神社だなんて
No wonder they haven't had any visitors.
（講釈師）
なるほど 人が来ないはずです
Who knew they were being treated like a haunted shrine?
まさか お化け神社扱い
されていたとは
Poor them.
トホホ
What is the matter, Nanami?
（巴衛）
どうした 奈々生
Tomoe...
巴衛
（巴衛）
買い物に行ったのではなかったか？
What happened to all the shopping you had planned?
What about you? What are you doing up there?
（奈々生）
巴衛こそ そこで何してんの
うん
鳥居に枝がかかってきたのでな
The branches have started to encroach on the torii gate,
so I was pondering whether I should cut them down.
枝を落とそうかと
思案していたのだ
（奈々生）
どうにかしたい
I have to fix this.
I know!
そうだ
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
We'll hold a festival at the shrine!
ミカゲ社で
秋祭りをするの
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
Mikage Shrine Autumn
Festival to Attract More
Worshippers Project
When they get here, they'll see that Mikage Shrine isn't a creepy, rundown ghost town.
そしたら 人も来るし―
ミカゲ社が怖い廃神社じゃないって
知ってもらえるよ
Wow! Fun! Count me in!
（瑞希(みずき)）
わあ 楽しそう！　僕 賛成
ばかばかしい
Ridiculous.
A sacred ritual isn't an excuse to have a party.
客寄せのための祭事など
俺は知らんからな
I will have nothing to do with this.
This brings back fond memories.
（鬼切(おにきり)）
懐かしいですね
We used to hold many sacred rituals back in the day.
（虎徹(こてつ)）
昔は 祭事も行われておりましたし
It's a mess.
（瑞希）
ごったごた
L-Lord Mikage requested that we not touch anything inside.
（鬼切）
ミカゲ様が 触るなと
おっしゃっておいででしたので
Oh! There!
あっ あれ おみこしじゃない？
Isn't this a sacred palanquin?
Hup!
Oh!
あっ いけない！
Oh, no!
うん？　何か…
What was that?
（虎徹）
な… 奈々生様
手を離してはなりませぬ
L-Lady Nanami, you must not let go!
Sorry!
（奈々生）
ごめん！
Now let's see how it looks.
さあ どんなのかな？
Shabby...
It's not so bad! We can make it work!
何とかなる 何とかなる
It just needs some paint and maybe some soap.
洗って塗装し直せば どうにか…
ひえーっ！
I can't believe she pulled that out.
あんな物を引っ張り出して
何をやっているのだ あいつは
What is she doing?
I could ask you the same thing, Tomoe.
巴衛君こそ 何やってんだよ
心配なら 手伝えばいいのに
If you're worried, you could just help her.
But honestly,
にしても 巴衛君って―
it's amazing to me how you refuse to see Nanami as anything other than a helpless human girl.
奈々生ちゃんは人間だって意識が
本当に強いんだね
When I look at her, I don't see anything less than a god.
僕は 神様にしか見えないけどな
She is the only one who sees herself as a human. It is all she will accept.
自分を人間としか見てないのは
奈々生のほうだ
ああ 結構 さまになってきたよね
It's starting to look pretty good, right?
Working hard there, I see.
（巴衛）ご苦労なことだな
（奈々生）うん？
Tomoe!
巴衛
見て 私の おみこし！
Look! My sacred palanquin!
ハァー
みこしは神の こし
生身の お前では乗れんだろう
Sacred palanquins are for gods.
As a human, you cannot ride it.
（巴衛）
お前に祭事は荷が重い
もう諦めたらどうだ
Sacred rituals are too great a burden for you.
Why not give it up already?
Not yet!
とりあえず みこしは保留で
他に 何か使える物はないかな
We'll set the palanquin aside for now.
I wonder if there's anything else that we can use...
全く お前は 懲りないやつだな
I swear, you never know when to stop, do you?
It is not as if the lack of worshipers is a recent thing.
昨日 今日
参拝者が消えたわけでもない
The shrine has been in this state long before you came.
お前が来る前から
社は こんな状態だったのだ
土地神になったからといって
気に病むことはない
Just because you are the land god does not mean you are held responsible.
You always keep the ablution pavilion clean,
and I want worshipers to use it.
（奈々生）
私は 巴衛が いつも きれいにする
ちょうずやを―
参拝者に使ってほしい
The shrine is absolutely spotless,
（奈々生）
社殿には
ちり一つ落ちてないし―
and there's no trash or anything in the offering box.
おさい銭箱にも
ごみなんて入ってないの
そういうのを
みんなに知ってほしいだけ
I just want everyone to know that.
そりゃ 私は 神様らしいこと
何もできないけど―
I mean, sure, I can't do anything godlike,
but if it's something a human can do, I can manage—
人ができる範囲なら
努力しだいで何とか…
It is only that you do not notice.
（巴衛）
お前が気付かないだけだ
What?
It is because of your presence that the air appears clear.
（巴衛）
ここの空気が澄んでいるのは
お前がいるからだ
Uninhabited shrines tend to attract a strong miasma in the air.
無人の社は しょう気の たまり場
Even I would be incapable of exorcising it.
いくら俺でも はらうことはできん
Think back to when you first arrived.
お前が初めて来たとき―
ここが どうだったか
覚えていよう
It has become considerably more beautiful, has it not?
随分 きれいになったと思わないか
（奈々生）
やっぱり 気味悪い廃神社なんて
言われたくない
I still don't want people talking about it like a shack!
出来た！　よし
It's done!
All right!
We're the Mikage Shrine!
（奈々生）
ミカゲ社で～す
お祭りをやるので来てくださ～い
We're holding a festival, so please come!
Mikage Shrine
Autumn Festival!
October 21st 5pm~
We will be waiting
for you at the
Mikage Shrine!
Mikage Shrine
Autumn Festival!
October 21st 5pm~
We will be waiting
for you at the
Mikage Shrine!
（奈々生）
はい
Here.
No way!
うそ！　廃神社じゃねえの？
I thought the shrine was abandoned!
It's not.
違うよ　きれいで いい所だから
It's beautiful and nice.
Time to go!
（男の子）行くぞ！
（女の子）ああーっ！
I hope you come!
（奈々生）
来てね～！　待ってるよ～！
I'll be waiting for you!
So the mortal god girl is conducting a sacred ritual?
（乙比古(おとひこ)）
人神の娘が 祭事ね…
Okay, we have one week until the festival.
というわけで
お祭りまで あと１週間
What kind of events should we hold?
どういうイベントを
行えばいいか―
I'm open to any suggestions you'd like to make.
何か提案があれば
聞かせてください
Me! I...
はい！　僕は…
Plan
want to prepare giant urns of sake and lavishly entertain the guests!
お酒を大がめに用意して
大盤振る舞いっていうのがいいな
Where do you hope to find that much sake?
どこに それだけの酒がある
You haven't even thrown an idea out!
You're in no position to criticize my suggestion!
アイデアを出しもしないで―
人の意見を批判するのは
どうかと思うよ！
（巴衛）なら…
（一同）ん？
Okay.
Plan
Why not capture a couple spirits and put them on display?
（巴衛）
何匹か妖怪を捕らえてきて
見せ物にでもすればいい
Dead
Serious
That sounds wonderful!
What'll I do? The way they think is too otherworldly.
（奈々生）
どうしよう
みんな浮世離れし過ぎて
どうしたらいいか…
Master Mizuki's idea is good too!
What do I do?
Food requires a permit from the Health Department, so you'd better not.
（鞍馬(くらま)）
食い物は
保健所からの許可がいるから―
やめたほうがいい
If it's a festival, you could
probably just do a ritual dance,
祭りなら
お神楽 舞ったりとか―
or let people draw their fortunes.
社務所で
おみくじでいいんじゃない？
Oh!
A ritual dance!
（鬼切）
神楽！
Drawing fortunes!
（虎徹）
みくじ！
That sounds great! You're amazing, Kurama!
それいい　すごい 鞍馬！
What are you doing here?!
なぜ お前が ここにいる
Nanami
I received a letter from Nanami.
（鞍馬）
奈々生に 手紙をもらったのさ
She was worried about planning events with the useless fox and his friends.
無能な きつねたちだけでは
心配だとな
Here you go. I bought you a gift.
はい これ 俺土産
銘菓“いも恋”
Yam Love. They're delicious.
Wow! Thank you!
Not pleased
（奈々生）
うわーっ！　鞍馬 ありがとう
神楽なら
昔 ここでも行われていたぞ
We had ritual dances performed here all the time at past events.
What?
I did not believe she would be interested, so I did not mention it.
奈々生では荷が重いだろうと思って
言わなかっただけだ
Oh-ho?
（瑞希･鞍馬）
ほう
It's beautiful!
きれい
Try it on over your clothes.
服の上からでよい　着てみるか？
If you'd like to.
What? Can I?
えっ いいの？
随分 さまになった
You wear it...
incredibly well.
R-Really?!
ほ… 本当？
You've taken such good care of the shrine. If you approve of me doing the dance,
社を大切に守ってきた
巴衛が認めてくれたから―
then I'm sure it'll go well.
きっと うまくいくよ
Perhaps.
そうだな
If we are doing this, we must do it in time for the festival.
やるからには
祭りに間に合わせるからな
There's not much time, so prepare to work hard.
厳しく教えるから 覚悟しておけ
I'll work hard!
頑張りま～す
right up
Next part coming
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Do Not
Remove
From Room
Right.
（巴衛）
右… 左… 前…
Left.
Front.
左… 右… 手 上げ過ぎ
Right. Your hand is too high.
Slow down more.
もっと ゆっくり
Good. And turn to your right there.
そう そこで 右に回って…
（巴衛）逆だ！
（奈々生）うわっ！
The other way!
When will you remember?
何度 言ったら 覚えるのだ
You only have a week to learn up to the ninth movement!
あと１週間で ９番まで
習得せねばならんのに―
１番で手間取ってる場合か！
Yet you're struggling with the first!
I'm trying, but you're going through it all so fast.
と… 巴衛の教えるテンポ
早すぎだよ
It is not fast at all.
早くない！
お前の物覚えが悪いのだ
You are a slow learner and must focus.
Days left until
the Mikage Shrine
Autumn Festival
さあ 何を休んでいる　続きだ
Come, what are you doing resting? Time to continue!
９番って そんなに長いの踊っても
誰も喜ばないよ
Nine movements?
No one wants to watch me for that long.
Oh, no, Lady Nanami!
（鬼切）
いいえ 奈々生様
It is the land god's duty to exorcise and cleanse the land of miasma.
土地の しょう気を
はらい清めるのは 土地神の仕事
This is the official revival of sacred rituals at our shrine...
（虎徹）
これは 我が社の
正式な祭事復活なのですから
...so please do it completely and perfectly!
（鬼切･虎徹）
完璧になさいませ！
It would help if we had music instead of just the drums.
太鼓だけじゃなくて―
音楽があれば
覚えやすいんだけどな
If you want music...
音楽なら…
Do we have some?
あるの？
Wheeeeeze
Mizuki is practicing it now.
今 瑞希が練習しているところだ
Wheeeeeze
He can't even make a sound yet!
（奈々生）
まだ 音も出せてないじゃん！
Wheeeeeze
Just do it!
いいから やれ！
最初から通して １本！
Rage
One more time from the top!
Y-Yes, sir!
は… はい！
Eep
We are going to
do awesome!
I don't consider myself a clumsy person,
そんな要領 悪いほうじゃ
ないはずだけど
but when he's around, I just totally...
いつものことながら
巴衛の前だと まるで気がせいて
get so anxious.
Your hand is too high.
手 上げ過ぎ
Wheeeeeze
Bzzzz
Owowowowow...
痛たた…
（障子が開く音）
（奈々生）うん？
Morning.
（巴衛）
おはよう
You will learn all the way to the fifth movement today.
今日は ５番まで覚えてもらう
ひぃーっ！　スパルタぎつね！
Ah, slave-driving fox alert!
Days left until
the Mikage Shrine
Autumn Festival
Your hand is too high.
（巴衛）
手 上げ過ぎ
Slow down more.
もっと ゆっくり
And turn to your right there.
そこで 右に回って
逆だ！
The other way!
Why are you making me repeat myself?
昨日と同じことを言わせるな！
Wheeeeeze
（鬼切･虎徹）
奈々生様 ファイトですぞ！
Don't give up, Lady Nanami!
何だ その動きは！
What is with the way you are moving?!
ひえーっ！
Wheeeeeze
Take a three and a half minute break.
（巴衛）
３分半 休憩だ
（奈々生）
ひい…
ハァー
Nanami.
奈々生
Huh?! What?!
ひいっ！　何… 休憩中でしょ！
I'm on break, right?!
手を出せ
Give me your hand.
What?
うまく踊らねばならないと
思うから緊張する
You're getting nervous because you're only thinking of achieving perfection.
It is this fear that is causing you to lose focus.
緊張するから うまく踊れない
緊張しているときは
こうするといい
When you are nervous,
this is what you should do.
ミカゲ社に伝わる
由緒ある おまじないだ
It is a spell with a storied history at the shrine.
What?
これを飲み込め
Swallow this.
どうだ　落ち着いただろう
Well?
You feel calmer, do you not?
Yeah.
It is used to help swallow fear.
人を飲むと言ってな
神としての自覚を持つ まじないだ
It also serves to remind you of your divinity.
You should be able to do well now.
これで うまくやれるだろう
Thank you.
ありがとう
But I already know that trick.
We used to play it on each other as kids.
でも これ 普通に私たちも
子供のころから使ってたけど…
Break is over!
（巴衛）
休憩 終わりだ！
（奈々生）
はい～！
Yes, sir!
Ow!
あ痛っ！
Momozono Nanami, age 17.
（乙比古）
桃園(ももぞの)奈々生 17歳
A typical high school girl you might find anywhere.
どこにでもいる平凡な女子高生
Appearance, C. Athleticism, D.
（乙比古）
容姿はＣ 運動能力Ｄ
霊力 通力 ともにＣ
Appearance
Athleticism
Spiritual power and divine power, both C.
Spiritual Power
Divine Power
Truly, not a single stand-out quality. Just your average human.
ホント 何一つ
いいとこない―
ただの人間
A super ordinary person... Not even.
超一般人以下
ハァー
Why did Mikage end up choosing a girl like her?
ミカゲ君は 何で こんな娘
選んじゃったのか 理解に苦しむわ
It's beyond my comprehension.
鳴神姫(なるかみひめ)のときも 海のときも
ちょっと試させてもらって…
Even that time with Lady Narukami and that day at the beach,
I took the liberty of testing her a little.
And I guess it looked like she pulled through in her own way, but...
まあ それなりに―
切り抜けてきたみたい
だったけど…
どうにも あの小娘に
土地神が務まる気がしないわ
I just don't get the feeling that
she's qualified to be a land god.
ミカゲ君の眼鏡も
曇ってたんじゃないかしら？
Maybe Mikage's glasses were clouded.
They are clean, I assure you.
（ミカゲ）
曇ってませんよ
わっ びっくり！
いたの ミカゲ君？
You scared me! How long have you been there?!
Long enough.
いましたよ
The girl has won my faith in her.
あの子は 僕の見込んだ娘です
Then I believe it's time for a final test.
じゃあ 最終テスト いってみる？
That is not it!
そうじゃない！
はい～！
Right. Left. Right. Turn to my right.
（奈々生）
右… 左… 右… 右にターン
あれ？　違う
Wait, that was wrong.
あっ あ痛たた…
Owowowowow...
Days left until
the Mikage Shrine
Autumn Festival
I can't even dance the first
movement all the way through.
まだ１番も
ちゃんと踊れないなんて―
What am I doing?
何やってんだろう
Tomoe has faith in me that I can do this.
巴衛は
私がやれるって信じてくれている
痛たた…
Owowowow!
Ow, that hurt.
痛たた…
（乙比古）
さっすが 運動能力Ｄの小娘
Now we know why you scored a D for athleticism. You suck!
（乙比古）下手っぴ
（奈々生）えっ？
What?
誰よ あんた
Who're you?!
（乙比古）
礼儀知らずな小娘ね
What an ill-mannered little girl.
In these situations,
こういうときは
身分の低い あんたから―
the one with lesser social standing should introduce herself first.
へりくだって名乗るもんよ
桃園奈々生ちゃん
Momozono Nanami.
H-How do you know my name?!
な… 何で私の名前？
Since you are going to hold a sacred festival in
Mikage's name, I must make sure you are worthy.
ミカゲの名前で
祭事をするからには―
試させてもらうわ
There will be a test to see if you can
really carry out the duties of a land god.
あんたが 本当に土地神の仕事を
こなせるかどうか
あ痛！
Ow!
Who the heck was he... or she?
何 今の おばさんみたいな
おじさんみたいな おばさん
Now go on.
さあ お行き
Exorcising this level of miasma should be no problem for a true land god.
土地神なら これくらいの しょう気
はらえるはず
Let's see what you've got, Nanami.
あんたに できるかしら
奈々生ちゃん
Miasma? But why?!
しょう気　どうして？
Everything was fine yesterday.
昨日までは 何ともなかったのに
Tomoe just finished cleaning the pavilion.
巴衛が きれいにしてくれた
ちょうずやが…
えっ？　何で
What? Why?
What the...
It is because of your presence that the air appears clear.
（巴衛）
ここの空気が澄んでいるのは
お前がいるからだ
Uninhabited shrines tend to attract a strong miasma in the air.
無人の社は しょう気の たまり場
Even I would be incapable of exorcising it.
いくら俺でも はらうことはできん
お前が初めて来たとき―
Think back to when you first arrived.
ここが どうだったか
覚えていよう
It has become considerably more beautiful, has it not?
随分きれいになったと
思わないか？
Calm down.
（奈々生）
落ち着いて　私 落ち着いて
Calm down.
Purify
Purify!
浄化！
What?
Beautify
Beautify!
美化！
Cleanse
掃除！
Cleanse!
Exorcise!
お祓(はら)い！
Exorcise
Purge!
お清め！
C-Clean... Clean!
ク… クリーン！　クリーン！
Please go away!
お願い いなくなって
お願い 消えて！
Please disappear!
Why?
何で…
God Beam! God Beam!
神様ビーム
神様…
God...
Morning, Nanami! I can make a sound now!
（瑞希）
おはよう 奈々生ちゃん
僕 音 出るようになったよ
Wheeeeeze
Huh?
（巴衛）
どういうことだ
What is going on here?
The miasma around the shrine has grown thicker!
社の周りの しょう気が
濃くなっている
Tomoe, this is weird, right?
（瑞希）
巴衛君　おかしいよね
昨日までは澄んでいたのに―
It was clear until yesterday.
Is Nanami's divine power not up to the task anymore?
奈々生ちゃんの通力が
及ばなくなってる？
Where is she?
奈々生は？
（巴衛）
奈々生！
Nanami!
（奈々生）
あっ 巴衛
Tomoe...
I tried to exorcise it, but...
はらおうとしたんだけど…
Nanami!
（瑞希）
奈々生ちゃん　大丈夫？
Are you okay?!
Mizuki, can you handle this?
（巴衛）
瑞希 はらえるか？
What? Don't be ridiculous.
えっ？　むちゃ言わないでよ
やってみるけど
But I'll give it a try.
The shrine...
社が…
Stay in bed.
寝ていろ
あとは 俺たちが何とかする
We will find a way to take care of this.
Exorcising miasma from the land is the land god's duty.
土地の しょう気をはらうのは
土地神の仕事
I have to do it.
私がやらなきゃ…
We do not need you.
お前はいい
Do not move from that spot.
ここを動くな
Do you have any more than that?!
（巴衛）
もっと ないのか
What do you think my precious sacred sake is?!
僕の貴重な神酒を
何だと思ってるのさ
And this is only a temporary solution.
それに これは一時しのぎ
乾けば効力がなくなる
Once it dries, it loses its effectiveness.
Could you be any more useless?!
使えないやつだな
何もできない君に
言われたくないよ！
You haven't even made an attempt, so I don't want to hear it!
I...
（奈々生）
私…
haven't even begun to live up to Tomoe's expectations.
ちっとも
巴衛の期待に応えられてない
I...
私…
am always being saved by him.
いつも
巴衛に助けてもらってばかり
The truth is...
本当は…
We do not need you.
お前は いい
I...
（奈々生）
私…
haven't accomplished anything.
何もできてない　何も…
Not a thing.
I...
私 必要とされてない
am not...
needed.
Nanami?!
奈々生？
Nanami...
奈々生
ah ah ah ah
Nanami!
（巴衛）
奈々生
奈々生！
Nanami!
ah ah ah ah
I'm going into town, Tomoe.
（ミカゲ）
街へ行ってくるよ 巴衛
ah ah ah ah
Where have you gone?
どこへ行った
ah ah ah ah
Nanami!
奈々生！
ah ah ah ah
kamisama onegai da
Please, God
boku no
I...
ano hito ni aitai no sa
I want to meet her
ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah
kamisama tsurain da
God, I'm in pain
kyou mo mata nou ni
Because, she...
konakatta
didn't come today either.
onegai ga aru no kamisama
I have a request, God
boku wo tasukete
Please, save me
ah ah ah ah
kamisama mou osoi
God, it's too late for me
ano ko wa...
Because she's...
Preview
Helpless in the face of the rampant miasma
at the shrine, Nanami runs away from home.
（講釈師）
ミカゲ社に はびこる
しょう気を前に―
Touku sora ni
gone off into the distant sky
どうすることもできず
逃げ出した奈々生
巴衛が必死に捜すも 見つからず
Tomoe looks for her, but cannot find her.
Kieta no sa
and disappeared
ああ このまま
２人は離れてしまうのか
Is this how it ends?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Next time, "I've Started The 'Being A God' Thing."
次回「神様はじめました」
I've Started The 'Being A God' Thing
Sayonara baby
Farewell, baby
最終話でございます　ご堪能あれ
It's the final episode!
Please enjoy every last minute of it!